Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - A
        - After The Fire - Der kommissar, 1982; SR-10499; After The Fire (Box 167)
        - Afterglow - It's just a song, 1991; SR-10500; Afterglow (Box 168)
          Catalog # DW 1924; A-side Matrix # DW1924
          Dance and Waves
        - Aftershock - She loves me, she loves me not, 1990; SR-10501; Aftershock (Box 168)
          Catalog # DMD 1578; A-side Matrix # STDM 59589 59590 59591-1
          Beverly Hills, California
        - A-G-2-A-KE - Sellin' dreams, 1998; SR-10502; A-G-2-A-KE (Box 168)
          Catalog # SPRO-13185; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-13185-1-7
          Rap-A-Lot Records
          Houston, Texas
        - A-G-2-A-KE - Hot club wax, 1998; SR-10503; A-G-2-A-KE (Box 168)
          Catalog # SPRO-13192; A-side Matrix # SPRO-7087-6-13192-1-7
        - A-G-2-A-KE - Hot club wax, 1998; SR-10504; A-G-2-A-KE (Box 168)
        - Age Of Chance - Kiss, 1986; SR-10505; Age Of Chance (Box 168)
          Catalog # PR 2007; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-51324-1
        - Age Of Chance - Crush collision, 1986; SR-10506; Age Of Chance (Box 168)
          Catalog # 70503; A-side Matrix # 70503 A 1
          Virgin Records
        - Agent 00 - The magnificent, 1997; SR-10507; Agent 00 (Box 168)
          Catalog # DJ Fern 002; A-side Matrix # DJ Fern 002
          Inferno Records
        - Agent Provocateur - Sabotage, 1996; SR-10508; Agent Provocateur (Box 168)
          Catalog # XPR 3047; A-side Matrix # 01 663291 20 1B1
          Wall Of Sound
        - Agent Orange - Bitchin' summer, 1982; SR-10509; Agent Orange (Box 168)
          Catalog # PBS 1037; A-side Matrix # PBS 1037 A
          Posh Boy
          Palm Desert, California
        - Agent Provocateur - Agent dan, 1997; SR-10510; Agent Provocateur (Box 168)
          Catalog # AGENT3PR12; A-side Matrix # AGENT3PR12
        - Agent Provocateur - The phat and ratty EP, 1997; SR-10511; Agent Provocateur (Box 168)
          Catalog # APHAT 1; A-side Matrix # APHAT-1
        - à;Grumh… - Bloody side, 1988; SR-10512; à;Grumh… (Box 168)
          Catalog # BIUS 2009; A-side Matrix # BIUS 2009-A1
          Play It Again Sam Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Aguabella, Francisco - Hitting hard, 1977; SR-10513; Aguabella, Francisco (Box 168)
          Catalog # E-8001; A-side Matrix # E8001-A
          Epsilon Records
        - Ahead Of Our Time - 21st century, 1975; SR-10514; Ahead Of Our Time (Box 168)
          Catalog # APL1-1189-A; A-side Matrix # APL1 1189A
          RCA Records
        - Ahmad - Come widdit, 1995; SR-10515; Ahmad; Ras Kass; Saafir (Box 168)
          Catalog # SPRO 50856; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50856-A
          Priority Records
        - Ailton & Binho - Quero mais..., 1995; SR-10516; Ailton & Binho (Box 168)
          Catalog # 443.002 A; A-side Matrix # 443002 A
          Afegan
          Brazil
        - Ailton & Binho - Quero mais..., 1995; SR-10517; Ailton & Binho (Box 168)
          Catalog # 443.025 A; A-side Matrix # 443025 A
        - Ailton & Binho - Quero mais..., 1995; SR-10518; Ailton & Binho (Box 168)
          Catalog # 443.026 A; A-side Matrix # 443026 A
        - AIR - Premiers Symptomes, 1999; SR-10519; AIR (Box 168)
          Catalog # 3098; A-side Matrix # 724 304 724 511 A
          Source
        - Air Power - Be yourself, 1979; SR-10520; Air Power (Box 168)
          Catalog # AVI-12-252-D; A-side Matrix # 118-12-252-A
          AVI Records
        - Aisha and Her "Mama" - Why, mama, why?, 1989; SR-10521; Aisha and Her "Mama" (Box 168)
          Catalog # MSB-1228; A-side Matrix # MSB-1228-A
          Mrs. B Records
          Miami, Florida
        - AK1200 - Junior's tune, 2002; SR-10522; AK1200 (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10523. Different discs
          Catalog # BBSAK002; A-side Matrix # BBSAK002 A
          Breakbeat Science Records
        - High Contrast - Return to forever, 2002; SR-10523; High Contrast (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10522. Different discs. Annotated (Sleeve)Possibly test pressing
          Catalog # BRK 34001; A-side Matrix # BBSCHOOLB1
        - A.K.A - Warning (Disc one), 1996; SR-10524; A.K.A (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10525. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # WARN 8; A-side Matrix # WARN8 A
          Parousia
        - A.K.A - Warning (Disc two), 1996; SR-10525; A.K.A (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10524. Double album
          Catalog # WARN 8; A-side Matrix # WARN8 C
        - Akafella - In your mouth; In the world, 1996; SR-10526; Akafella (Box 168)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # AK-001-A
          Stress Entertainment
        - Akasha - Brown sugar, 1997; SR-10527; Akasha (Box 168)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # WALLT 028 XA-3-1-1
        - Akasha - Brown sugar, 1997; SR-10528; Akasha (Box 168)
          Catalog # WALLT 028; A-side Matrix # WALL T 028-A2
        - Akasha - Cinematique, 1998; SR-10529; Akasha (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10530. Double album
          Catalog # WALL LP016; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 016-A1
        - Akasha - Cinematique, 1998; SR-10530; Akasha (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10529. Double album
          Catalog # WALL LP016; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 016-C1
        - Akasha - Jazadelica EP, 1994; SR-10531; Akasha (Box 168)
          Catalog # WALLT 003; A-side Matrix # WALLT003A
        - Akasha - Spanish fly, 1996; SR-10532; Akasha (Box 168)
          Catalog # WALLT 020; A-side Matrix # WALL T 020-A1
        - Akasha - Spanish fly, 1996; SR-10533; Akasha (Box 168)
          Catalog # WALLT020; A-side Matrix # WALL T 020 A1
        - AKB - Rhythmic feet, 1979; SR-10534; AKB (Box 168)
          Catalog # RS-1-3057; A-side Matrix # RS-1-3057-AS-CT-1
          RSO
        - Akendengue, Pierre - Espoir a soweto, 1988; SR-10535; Akendengue, Pierre (Box 168)
          Catalog # ENC 141; A-side Matrix # ENC 141 A
          Encore!
        - Akhenaton - Métèque et mat (Disc one), 1995; SR-10536; Akhenaton (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10537. Double album
          Catalog # 7243 8 40784 1 6; A-side Matrix # 7243-8-40784-1-6-A
          Delabel
        - Akhenaton - Métèque et mat (Disc two), 1995; SR-10537; Akhenaton (Box 168)
          In same jacket as # SR-10536. Double album
          Catalog # 7243 8 40784 1 6; A-side Matrix # 7243-8-40784-1-6-C
        - Akinyele - Loud hangover, 1995; SR-10538; Akinyele; Sadat X (Box 168)
          Catalog # RDAB 64449-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64449-1-A1
          Loud Records
        - Akinyele - Love me for free, 1996; SR-10539; Akinyele (Box 168)
          Catalog # ZP-17213-1-A; A-side Matrix # ZP17213-1-A
          Zoo Entertainment
        - Akinyele - In the world, 1996; SR-10540; Akinyele (Box 168)
          Catalog # ZP-17206-1-A; A-side Matrix # 72445-14266-1A1
        - Akon - Locked up, 2004; SR-10541; Akon; Styles P. (Box 168)
          Catalog # B0002245-11; A-side Matrix # B000224511-A
        - Akon - Operations of nature, 1996; SR-10542; Akon; A-kon (Box 168)
          Catalog # ED 5803; A-side Matrix # ST-ED-5803A-1
          Eastwest Records
        - Akon - Locked up, 2003; SR-10543; Akon (Box 168)
          Catalog # UNIR 21143-1; A-side Matrix # UNIR-21143-1-A
        - Aksion - Doin' it; They don't know, 1987; SR-10544; Aksion (Box 168)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # KWE-001-A
          KW Entertainment
        - Aku-Aku - The night belongs to Charlie, 1984; SR-10545; Aku-Aku (Box 168)
          Catalog # SH 1966; A-side Matrix # SH1966A
          Shatter Records
        - Aku-Aku - No expression, 1987; SR-10546; Aku-Aku (Box 168)
          Catalog # PDI-9005; A-side Matrix # PDI-9005A-1
        - Al'Tariq - Think not, 1996; SR-10547; Al'Tariq (Box 168)
          Catalog # SPR09915; A-side Matrix # SPR0 9915 A
          Correct Records
        - Al'Tariq - Think not, 1996; SR-10838; Al'Tariq (Box 168)
        - Alabina - Alabina (The Remixes), 1996; SR-10548; Alabina; Ishtar; Ninos de Sara (Box 168)
          Catalog # 27174-6; A-side Matrix # DFI 96-5 271 74-6 A
          Ascot Music
        - A'lan - A'lan's groove, 1986; SR-10549; A'lan (Box 168)
          Catalog # MRC-0931; A-side Matrix # L10732 MRC-0931-A
          Macola Record Company
        - Alanda - Night by night, 1990; SR-10550; Alanda (Box 168)
          Catalog # ID 10003; A-side Matrix # ID 10003 A
          ID Records
        - Alansky, Jay - A reminiscent drive, 2003; SR-10551; Alansky, Jay (Box 168)
          Catalog # F174W1; A-side Matrix # B272g7g-01 A1
          F Communications
        - Albanese, Judy - You, 1999; SR-10552; Albanese, Judy (Box 169)
          Catalog # CMC-1006-P2-1; A-side Matrix # CMC-1006-P2-A
          Contagious Records
        - Albino Twins - We're not going for it; Get busy with it, 1986; SR-10553; Albino Twins (Box 169)
          Catalog # TG 004; A-side Matrix # TG-004-A
          Turngold Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Albright, Gerald - Feeling inside, 1988; SR-10554; Albright, Gerald (Box 169)
          . Annotated (Sleeve)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # STPR-56141-1
          Atlantic Records
        - Aleem - Love's on fire, 1986; SR-10555; Aleem; Burgess, Leroy (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10556. 2 copies
          Catalog # DMD 924; A-side Matrix # STDM 49156-1
        - Aleem - Love's on fire, 1986; SR-10556; Aleem; Burgess, Leroy (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10555. 2 copies
        - Aleem - Why Hawaii, 1996; SR-10557; Aleem (Box 169)
          Catalog # HARD18 12 DJ; A-side Matrix # HARD-1812-A1
          Concrete
        - Aleems - Confusion, 1985; SR-10558; Aleems; Aleem (Box 169)
          Catalog # DMD 897; A-side Matrix # ST DM 48706-1
        - Alexander, Goldie - Knocking down love, 1983; SR-10559; Alexander, Goldie (Box 169)
          Catalog # QUS 036; A-side Matrix # QUS-036-A
          TGO
          Ontario, Canada
        - Alexander, Goldie - Show you my love, 1981; SR-10560; Alexander, Goldie (Box 169)
          Catalog # CP 713; A-side Matrix # CP-713-MA
          Artista
        - Alexkid - Bienvenida (Remixes), 2001; SR-10561; Alexkid (Box 169)
          Catalog # F 147; A-side Matrix # B151968-01 A1
        - Alexis, Jamie - Lily of the streets; Mickey the dope..., 1990; SR-10562; Alexis, Jamie (Box 169)
          Catalog # AVL-90032LP; A-side Matrix # AVL-90032-A
          B-Down Records
          Boston, Massachusetts
        - Alfredo - Alfredo de la fe, 1979; SR-10563; Alfredo (Box 169)
          Catalog # LPV 473; A-side Matrix # LPC-473-A-1
          Criollo Records
          Palisades Park, New Jersey
        - Ali - Love letters, 1997; SR-10564; Ali; J.P. Esq. (Box 169)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # ALI002-A
          Island Black Music
        - Ali - Crucial grooves, 1997; SR-10565; Ali (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10566. 2 copies
          Catalog # PR12 7635-1; A-side Matrix # PR12 7635 1 A
        - Ali - Crucial grooves, 1997; SR-10566; Ali (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10565. 2 copies
        - Ali, Moontas - Rat race, 1985; SR-10567; Ali, Moontas (Box 169)
          Catalog # CM 533 A; A-side Matrix # CM-532-A
          Clarence Music Records
        - Alie, Marijosé - Caressé moin, 1987; SR-10568; Alie, Marijosé (Box 169)
          Catalog # 885 751-1; A-side Matrix # 222 885751 1 // 1 380
          Productions Phonographiques Françaises
        - Alien Nation - Tell me; Electric lady, 1994; SR-10569; Alien Nation (Box 169)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # 7-8863-51160-1-A-RE
          Pallas Records
        - Alisha - All night passion, 1984; SR-10570; Alisha (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10571. 2 copies
          Catalog # SPV 72-A; A-side Matrix # SPV-72-A1A-DJ
          Vanguard
        - Alisha - All night passion, 1984; SR-10571; Alisha (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10570. 2 copies
        - Alisha - Baby talk, 1985; SR-10572; Alisha (Box 169)
          Catalog # SPV 89-A; A-side Matrix # SPV-89A
        - Alisha - Baby talk, 1985; SR-10573; Alisha (Box 169)
        - Alisha - Into my secret, 1987; SR-10574; Alisha (Box 169)
          Catalog # 6432-1-RDXCD; A-side Matrix # 6432-1-RDXC-10-1
        - Alisha - Stargazing, 1986; SR-10575; Alisha (Box 169)
          Catalog # SPV 90-A; A-side Matrix # SPV-90-A-3
        - Alisha - Stargazing, 1986; SR-10576; Alisha (Box 169)
        - Alix - Jam to the beat, 1989; SR-10577; Alix (Box 169)
          Catalog # USA 3002; A-side Matrix # USA 3002-A
          Mackenzie Records
          Belgium
        - Alkaholiks - Mary Jane; Relieve yourself, 1994; SR-10578; Alkaholiks (Box 169)
          Catalog # 07863 62880-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-62880-1-A-1S
          The RCA Records Label
        - Alkaholiks - Mary Jane; Relieve yourself, 1994; SR-10579; Alkaholiks (Box 169)
          Catalog # RDAB 62880-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-62880-1-A-1S
        - Alkaholiks - Daam! Buckwild remix, 1995; SR-10580; Alkaholiks (Box 169)
          Catalog # RDAB 64303-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64303-1-A1
          RCA
        - Alkaholiks - The next level, 1995; SR-10581; Alkaholiks (Box 169)
          Catalog # RDAB 64319-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64319-1-A
        - All City - The hot joint, 1998; SR-10582; All City (Box 169)
          Catalog # MCA 13268; A-side Matrix # MCA-13268
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - Allnighters - Black is black, 1995; SR-10583; Allnighters (Box 169)
          Catalog # DOS 023; A-side Matrix # None
          Dos or Die Recordings
        - All Seeing I - Beat goes on, 1997; SR-10584; All Seeing I (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10585. 2 copies
          Catalog # FX 334; A-side Matrix # FX 334 A
          London Records
        - All Seeing I - Beat goes on, 1997; SR-10585; All Seeing I (Box 169)
          In same jacket as # SR-10584. 2 copies
        - All The Kings Men - Break the ice, 1986; SR-10586; All The Kings Men (Box 169)
          Catalog # SUD 057DJ; A-side Matrix # SUD-057-C
          Sutra Records
        - All The Way - She dropped a dime on me, 1988; SR-10587; All The Way (Box 169)
          Catalog # OTS 6543; A-side Matrix # OTS-6543-A
          On The Strength Records
        - Allan, Scott - I think we're alone now; Will you love me tomorrow, 1979; SR-10588; Allan, Scott (Box 169)
          Catalog # 426; A-side Matrix # TKD-426-A
          T.K. Disco
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Allen, Debbie - Special look, 1989; SR-10589; Allen, Debbie (Box 169)
          Catalog # MCA-6317; A-side Matrix # MCA9001FDS-1
        - Allen, Donna - Joy and pain, 1988; SR-10590; Allen, Donna (Box 169)
          Catalog # PR 2584; A-side Matrix # STDM-56486-2
          Oceana Records
          Netherlands
        - Allen, Peter - Don't wish too hard, 1979; SR-10591; Allen, Peter (Box 169)
          Catalog # SP-17072; A-side Matrix # SP17127-S M2
          Santa Monica, California
        - Allen, Peter - Don't wish too hard, 1979; SR-10592; Allen, Peter (Box 169)
          Catalog # SP-17081; A-side Matrix # SP17145-RC1
        - Allen, Scott - Guitarzan, 1984; SR-10593; Allen, Scott (Box 169)
          Catalog # 8380; A-side Matrix # CAR 8380 A
          Carrere
        - Allen, Tony - No accommodation for Lagos, 2000; SR-10594; Allen, Tony; Afrika 70 (Box 169)
          Catalog # STRUTALP002; A-side Matrix # STRUTALP 002 A-1-1-1
          Afro Strut
        - Allen, Tony - N.E.P.A; Never expect power always, 1984; SR-10595; Allen, Tony; Afrobeat 2000 (Box 169)
          Catalog # MT 002; A-side Matrix # MT-002-A
          Moving Target
        - Allenko Brotherhood Ensemble - The man with the drum, 2000; SR-10596; Allenko Brotherhood Ensemble (Box 169)
          Catalog # Comet 013; A-side Matrix # COMET 013 A
          Comet Records
        - Allenko Brotherhood Ensemble - Dance of Loa, 2000; SR-10597; Allenko Brotherhood Ensemble (Box 169)
          Catalog # Comet 015; A-side Matrix # COMET 15 A
        - Allentini, Georgio - Sexappeal, 1986; SR-10598; Allentini, Georgio (Box 169)
          Catalog # PPR-3563; A-side Matrix # L-10851/PPR-3563-A
          Picture Perfect Records
        - Allez Allez - Valley of the kings, 1982; SR-10655; Allez Allez (Box 169)
          Catalog # VS 556-12; A-side Matrix # VS 556 12 A1
        - Allfrumtha I - Fill my cup (to tha rim), 1998; SR-10656; Allfrumtha I (Box 169)
          Catalog # SPRO 81058; A-side Matrix # SPRO-81058-A
        - Allfrumtha I - County jail, 1998; SR-10601; Allfrumtha I (Box 169)
          Catalog # SPRO 30232; A-side Matrix # S-36870-RE1
        - Alliance Ethnik - Respect, 1995; SR-10602; Alliance Ethnik (Box 169)
          Catalog # 7243 8 927746 3; A-side Matrix # DE-8927746-A
        - Alliance Ethnik - Fat comeback, 1998; SR-10603; Alliance Ethnik (Box 169)
          Catalog # 7243 8955466; A-side Matrix # 72438955466 A
        - Alliance Ethnik - Simple and funky (Disc one), 1995; SR-10604; Alliance Ethnik (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10605; SR-10606; SR-10607. Double album; 2 copies
          Catalog # DE 7243 8 40161 1 1; A-side Matrix # 8401611-A
        - Alliance Ethnik - Simple and funky (Disc one), 1995; SR-10605; Alliance Ethnik (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10604; SR-10606; SR-10607. Double album; 2 copies
        - Alliance Ethnik - Simple and funky (Disc two), 1995; SR-10606; Alliance Ethnik (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10604; SR-10605; SR-10607. Double album; 2 copies
          Catalog # DE 7243 8 40161 1 1; A-side Matrix # 8401611-C
        - Alliance Ethnik - Simple and funky (Disc two), 1995; SR-10607; Alliance Ethnik (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10604; SR-10605; SR-10606. Double album; 2 copies
        - Allure - Oh oh; Hate 2 luv ya, 2005; SR-10608; Allure; Elephant Man (Box 170)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # UhOh A
          Tru Warier Records
        - Allure - Head over heels, 1996; SR-10609; Allure; Nas (Box 170)
          Catalog # HAS 9280; A-side Matrix # HAS-9280-A
        - Allure - Head over heels, 1997; SR-10610; Allure; Nas (Box 170)
          Catalog # XPR 3139; A-side Matrix # 31 3139 20 1A1
        - Allure - Enjoy yourself (Disc one), 2001; SR-10611; Allure; LL Cool J; Loon from Bad Boy (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10612. Double album
          Catalog # MCAR-25596-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR255961A
          Music Corporation of America
        - Allure - Enjoy yourself (Disc two), 2001; SR-10612; Allure (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10611. Double album
          Catalog # MCAR-25596-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR255961C
        - Allure - Kool wit me, 2001; SR-10613; Allure; All Star (Box 170)
          Catalog # MCAR-25627-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR256271A
        - Alonso, Darcy - Love grows stronger, 1988; SR-10614; Alonso, Darcy (Box 170)
          Catalog # FMS 62316; A-side Matrix # FMS-62316-A
          Select Records
        - Alonso, Maria Conchita - Atacame, 1985; SR-10615; Alonso, Maria Conchita (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-17376; A-side Matrix # A&MSP017376-A RCA2
          A&M Records
        - Alpert, Herb - Beyond, 1980; SR-10616; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-12034; A-side Matrix # A&M SP012034A(LONG)-S2
        - Alpert, Herb - Beyond, 1980; SR-10617; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
        - Alpert, Herb - Keep your eye on me, 1987; SR-10618; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-12226; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012226-A ES1
        - Alpert, Herb - Diamonds, 1987; SR-10619; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-12231; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-012231-A ES3
        - Alpert, Herb - Magic man, 1981; SR-10620; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-017163-A; A-side Matrix # A&M SP017163A-S2
        - Alpert, Herb - Rise, 1979; SR-10621; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP 12022; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 120435-K2
        - Alpert, Herb - Push and pull, 1982; SR-10622; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-17197; A-side Matrix # A&M SP017197A-T2
        - Alpert, Herb - The beat of the brass, 1968; SR-10623; Alpert, Herb; Tijuana Brass (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-4146; A-side Matrix # A&M SP4191-1
        - Alpert, Herb - Greatest hits, 1970; SR-10624; Alpert, Herb; Tijuana Brass (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-4245; A-side Matrix # R 100295A
        - Alpert, Herb - Diamonds, 1987; SR-10625; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-17475; A-side Matrix # A&M SP-017475-A ES-1
        - Alpert, Herb - Christmas album, 1981; SR-10626; Alpert, Herb; Tijuana Brass (Box 170)
          Catalog # SP-3113; A-side Matrix # A&M SP 03113-A P8
        - Alpert, Herb - Rotation, 1979; SR-10627; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10628. 2 copies
          Catalog # SP-12032; A-side Matrix # A&M SP012032A-K6
        - Alpert, Herb - Rotation, 1979; SR-10628; Alpert, Herb (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10627. 2 copies
        - Alpha Prhyme - Misanthropic, 1997; SR-10629; Alpha Prhyme (Box 170)
          Catalog # BD001; A-side Matrix # BD 01 B-01-01-1
          Big Dada Records
        - Alpinestars - Interlaken, 2001; SR-10630; Alpinestars (Box 170)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # FH12-019 A-01-1-1
          Faith and Hope Records Limited
          Manchester, United Kingdom
        - Alston, Jazz Lee - Love… never that, 1995; SR-10631; Alston, Jazz Lee (Box 170)
          Catalog # PRO-A-7428; A-side Matrix # PRO A 7428 A SRI
          American Recordings
        - Alston, Shirley - Shadda-da-da-da, 1981; SR-10632; Alston, Shirley (Box 170)
          Catalog # RRD-2208; A-side Matrix # RR-2208-12-A
          Red Rooster Records
        - Alston, Wallena - Let's go, let's go, 1997; SR-10633; Alston, Wallena (Box 170)
          Catalog # ALYONS; A-side Matrix # ALYONS-A
          Alyons Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - A.L.T. - Tequila, 1992; SR-10634; A.L.T.; Lost Civilization (Box 170)
          Catalog # 0-96161; A-side Matrix # STDM 62389-62590-1
          ATCO Records
        - Alter Ego - Betty Ford, 2000; SR-10635; Alter Ego (Box 170)
          Catalog # KLANG 38; A-side Matrix # KLANGELEKTRONIK 38
          Klang Elektronik
        - Always, Billy - My first love, 1982; SR-10636; Always, Billy (Box 170)
          Catalog # TAS-33119; A-side Matrix # TAS-33-119-A
          Waylo
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - Always, Billy - Back on track, 1988; SR-10637; Always, Billy (Box 170)
          Catalog # 49 07880; A-side Matrix # XSS07880A-1A
        - AM-FM - Hip hop (skable-de-wop); All we want is go-go, 1985; SR-10638; AM-FM (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10639. 2 copies
          Catalog # TDE-3009-A; A-side Matrix # TDE-30009-A
          T.T.E.D. Records
        - AM-FM - Hip hop (skable-de-wop); All we want is go-go, 1985; SR-10639; AM-FM (Box 170)
          In same jacket as # SR-10638. 2 copies
        - AM-FM - The word, 1987; SR-10640; AM-FM (Box 170)
          Catalog # TDE-LP-3033-A; A-side Matrix # GOGOUSA-3033-A
          Go Go USA Records
          Maryland
        - Amari - Callin' (Remix), 1998; SR-10641; Amari (Box 170)
          Catalog # TB 314 A; A-side Matrix # TB314A
          Tommy Boy
        - Amari - Callin', 1998; SR-10837; Amari (Box 170)
          Catalog # TB 448A; A-side Matrix # TB-444-RE2-A
        - Amazin Jewel T - Bring on the sleigh bells, 1991; SR-10642; Amazin Jewel T; Jewel T. (Box 170)
          Catalog # HIP 009; A-side Matrix # HIP-009-A
          Hip Hop Recordings
        - Amazulu - Mony mony, 1987; SR-10643; Amazulu (Box 170)
          Catalog # 1C K 060-2 02135 6; A-side Matrix # 2021356-A1
          EMI Electrola